Guide to the Washington Theater Club records, 1952-1983 MS2061
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Administrative files, 1952-1983; MS2061 Series 2
  - Royalties, Production 73, Curse You, Spread Eagle, 1971 (Box 128, Folder 1509)
  - Royalties, Staged Reading19, Claw Man, 1971 (Box 128, Folder 1510)
  - Royalties, Staged Reading 20, Sleep & Put on Your Potato Jacket, 1971 (Box 128, Folder 1511)
  - Royalties, Staged Reading 21, Clown, 1971 (Box 128, Folder 1512)
  - Royalties, Staged Reading 22, Out of Sight, 1971 (Box 128, Folder 1513)
  - Royalties, Staged Reading 23, The Presentation & Sundays Aren't What The Used to Be & Ladies Day, 1971 (Box 128, Folder 1514)
  - Royalties, Staged Reading 24, The Deadly Delilah, 1971 (Box 128, Folder 1515)
  - Royalties, Staged Reading 25, A Little Singing & A Little Dancing, 1971 (Box 128, Folder 1516)
  - Royalties, Staged Reading & Carnival Part 27, Stations: Madama Cleo Here, at Your Service & Playground, 1971 (Box 128, Folder 1517)
  - Royalties, Other Royalty Information, 1971 (Box 128, Folder 1518)
  - Royalties, Production 74, Lemon Sky, 1972 (Box 128, Folder 1519)
  - Royalties, Production 75, The Philanthropist, 1972 (Box 128, Folder 1520)
  - Royalties, Production 76, Washington Square, 1972 (Box 128, Folder 1521)
  - Royalties, Production 77, The Basement & Deadl Delilah & Animal, 1972 (Box 128, Folder 1522)
  - Royalties, Production 78, Lady Audley's Secret, 1972 (Box 129, Folder 1523)
  - Royalties, Production 79, Spread Eagle Papers, 1972 (Box 129, Folder 1524)
  - Royalties, Production 80, The Rapists, 1972 (Box 129, Folder 1525)
  - Royalties, Production 81, The Boys from Syracuse, 1972 (Box 129, Folder 1526)
  - Royalties, Staged Reading 28, Monolith, 1972 (Box 129, Folder 1527)
  - Royalties, Staged Reading 29, The Wizard of Spruce Street, 1972 (Box 129, Folder 1528)
  - Royalties, Staged Reading 30, Fire on Water, 1972 (Box 129, Folder 1529)
  - Royalties, Staged Reading 31, The Night Watchman, 1972 (Box 129, Folder 1530)
  - Royalties, Staged Reading 32, Thanksgiving at Aunt Betty's, 1972 (Box 129, Folder 1531)
  - Royalties, Staged Reading 33, Wild Bill, 1972 (Box 129, Folder 1532)
  - Royalties, Other Royalty Information, 1972 (Box 129, Folder 1533)
  - Royalties, Production 82, Ceremonies in Dark Old Men, 1973 (Box 129, Folder 1534)
  - Royalties, Production 83,The Enclave-, 1973 (Box 129, Folder 1535)
  - Royalties, Production 84, Scenes from American Life, 1973 (Box 129, Folder 1536)
  - Royalties, Production 85, The Ecstasy of Rita Joe, 1973 (Box 129, Folder 1537)
  - Royalties, Production 86, Something Wild, 1973 (Box 129, Folder 1538)
  - Royalties, Production 87, Inner City, 1973 (Box 129, Folder 1539)
  - Royalties, Production 88, Difficult Borning, 1973 (Box 129, Folder 1540)
  - Royalties, Other Royalty Information, 1973 (Box 129, Folder 1541)
  - Washington Drama Center Finances, 1953-1954 (Box 130, Folder 1542)
  - Theater Training Finances, 1958-1961 (Box 130, Folder 1543)
  - Theater Training Administration 1, 1960-1963 (Box 130, Folder 1544)
  - Theater Training Finances, 1961-1963 (Box 130, Folder 1545)
  - Theater Training Administration, 1963-1967 (Box 130, Folder 1546)
  - Accreditation Study, 1966 (Box 130, Folder 1547)
  - Theater Training Finances, 1966-1967 (Box 130, Folder 1548)
  - Theater Training School, District of Columbia Grant, 1967 August 19 (Box 131, Folder 1549)
  - Theater Training School, School and Community Expansion Proposal, 1967-1968 (Box 131, Folder 1550)
  - Theater Training School, Theater Training Finances, 1967-1968 (Box 131, Folder 1551)
  - Theater Training School, Adult Class Payments, 1967-1968 (Box 131, Folder 1552)
  - Theater Training School, Contract for Room, Montgomery County Jewish Community, Sept. 19-Nov. 28, undated (Box 131, Folder 1553)
  - Theater Training School, One-Act Play Tournament Executive Committee Participant: Hazel Wentworth, 1967-1969 (Box 131, Folder 1554)
  - Theater Training School, Extra Curricular Activities Working Party Study Group, D.C. Participant: Hazel Wentworth, 1968 (Box 131, Folder 1555)
  - Theater Training School, Theater Training Administration, 1968-1969 (Box 131, Folder 1556)
  - Theater Training School, Theater Training Finances, 1968-1969 (Box 131, Folder 1557)
  - Theater Training School, Adult Class Payments, 1968-1969 (Box 131, Folder 1558)
  - Theater Training School, Hattie M. Strong Grant, July 12, undated (Box 131, Folder 1559)
  - Theater Training School, Instructor: Frank Johns, undated (Box 131, Folder 1967)
  - Theater Training School, Purpose: Scholarships. Instructor: Harry Poe, undated (Box 131, Folder 1969)
  - Theater Training School, Theater Training Administration, 1969-1970 (Box 132, Folder 1560)
  - Theater Training School, Theater Training Finances, 1969-1970 (Box 132, Folder 1561)
  - Theater Training School, Theater Training Administration, 1970-1971 (Box 132, Folder 1562)
  - Theater Training School, Theater Training Finances, 1970-1971 (Box 132, Folder 1563)
  - Theater Training School, Contracts Purpose: Occupancy Permit, Summer in the Parks, & Directors' Training Workshop, 1970-1975 (Box 132, Folder 1564)
  - Theater Training School, Adult Theater Training Surveys, 1971 (Box 132, Folder 1565)
  - Theater Training School, Veterans Training Forms, 1971 (Box 132, Folder 1566)
  - Theater Training School, Theater Training Administration, 1971-1972 (Box 132, Folder 1567)
  - Theater Training School, Theater Training Finances, Oct.-Jan., 1971-1972 (Box 132, Folder 1568)
  - Theater Training School, Theater Training Finances, Jan.-Aug., 1972 (Box 133, Folder 1569)
  - Theater Training School, Adult Class Payments, 1971-1972 (Box 133, Folder 1570)
  - Theater Training School, Theater Training Administration, 1972-1973 (Box 133, Folder 1571)
  - Theater Training School, Theater Training Finances, 1972-1973 (Box 133, Folder 1572)
  - Theater Training School, Adult Class Payments, 1972-1973 (Box 133, Folder 1573)
  - Theater Training School, Theater Training Administration, 1973-1974 (Box 133, Folder 1574)
  - Proposals, undated (Box 133, Folder 1574a)
  - Acting Workshop, Jill Halloran, 1971-1972 (Box 134, Folder 1575)
  - Advanced Acting, Davey Marlin-Jones, 1967 April 19 (Box 134, Folder 1576)
  - Advanced Acting, Davey Marlin-Jones, 1967 October 18 (Box 134, Folder 1577)
  - Advanced Acting Davey Marlin-Jones, 1968 January 17 (Box 134, Folder 1578)
  - Advanced Acting Davey Marlin-Jones, 1968 January 17 (Box 134, Folder 1579)
  - Advanced Acting Davey Marlin-Jones, 1968 April 16 (Box 134, Folder 1580)
  - Advanced Acting Davey Marlin-Jones, 1968 April 17 (Box 134, Folder 1581)
  - Advanced Acting Ralph Strait, 1968 July 10 (Box 134, Folder 1582)
  - Advanced Acting Ralph Strait, 1968 October 01 (Box 134, Folder 1583)
  - Advanced Acting Davey Marlin-Jones, 1969 January 14 (Box 134, Folder 1584)
  - Advanced Acting, Davey Marlin-Jones, 1969 April 01 (Box 134, Folder 1585)
  - Advanced Acting, Davey Marlin-Jones, 1970 February 12 (Box 134, Folder 1586)
  - Advanced Acting, Jan.3-Stephen Aaron, 1972 May 22 (Box 134, Folder 1587)
  - Advanced Acting, Jan.8- Stephen Aaron, 1973 March 12 (Box 134, Folder 1588)
  - Basic Acting, Davey Marlin-Jones, 1966 March 08 (Box 134, Folder 1589)
  - Basic Acting, Karen Cross, 1966 July (Box 134, Folder 1590)
  - Adult Training, Basic Acting, Davey Marlin-Jones, 1966 September 27 (Box 135, Folder 1591)
  - Adult Training, Basic Acting, Davey Marlin-Jones, 1967 January 10 (Box 135, Folder 1592)
  - Adult Training, Basic Acting, Davey Marlin-Jones, 1967 February 26 (Box 135, Folder 1593)
  - Adult Training, Basic Acting, Tom Croft, 1967 June 26 (Box 135, Folder 1594)
  - Adult Training, Basic Acting, Jo Deodato, 1967 October 19 (Box 135, Folder 1595)
  - Adult Training, Basic Acting, Damon Brazwell, 1968 January 18 (Box 135, Folder 1596)
  - Adult Training, Basic Acting, Jo Deodato, 1968 January 18-March 14 (Box 135, Folder 1597)
  - Adult Training, Basic Acting, Jo Deodato, 1968 April 19-May (Box 135, Folder 1598)
  - Adult Training, Basic Acting, Jo Deodato Jul.8-24, 1968 (Box 135, Folder 1599)
  - Adult Training, Basic Acting, Jo Deodato, 1968 April 09-August 01 (Box 135, Folder 1600)
  - Adult Training, Basic Acting, Jo Deodato, 1968 October 02 (Box 135, Folder 1601)
  - Adult Training, Basic Acting I, Jo Doedato, 1969 October 01-November (Box 135, Folder 1602)
  - Adult Training, Basic Acting II, Nov. Jo Deodato, 1969 (Box 135, Folder 1603)
  - Adult Training, Basic Acting, Jo Deodato, 1970 March 02 (Box 135, Folder 1604)
  - Adult Training, Basic Acting, Jo Deodato, 1972 (Box 135, Folder 1605)
  - Adult Training, Directing, Davey Marlin-Jones, 1968 January 16 (Box 136, Folder 1606)
  - Adult Training, Directing, Davey Marlin-Jones, 1968 April 16 (Box 136, Folder 1607)
  - Adult Training, Directing, Davey Marlin-Jones, 1968 November 13 (Box 136, Folder 1608)
  - Adult Training, Directing, Davey Marlin-Jones, 1969 March 31 (Box 136, Folder 1609)
  - Adult Training, Directors' Training Workshop, Davey Marlin-Jones, 1970 October 20-December 16 (Box 136, Folder 1610)
  - Adult Training, Ensemble Acting Workshop, Anthony Abeson, 1972 April 05-August 08 (Box 136, Folder 1611)
  - Adult Training, Improvisation, Alton Miller, 1961 June 20-August 10 (Box 136, Folder 1612)
  - Adult Training, Intermediate Acting, Ralph Strait, 1968 September 30 (Box 136, Folder 1613)
  - Adult Training, Intermediate Acting, Leonard Yorr, 1970 February 16 (Box 136, Folder 1614)
  - Adult Training, Intermediate Acting, 1972 January 03-May 22 (Box 136, Folder 1615)
  - Adult Training, Journeyman Workshop, Logan Ramsey, 1959 October 11-1960 May 28 (Box 136, Folder 1616)
  - Adult Training, Journeyman Workshop, Logan Ramsey, 1960 October 09 (Box 136, Folder 1617)
  - Adult Training, Lyric Theater, Geoffrey Holder, 1974 July 28 (Box 136, Folder 1618)
  - Adult Training, Mime, Lou Gilbert June-Aug., 1969 (Box 136, Folder 1619)
  - Adult Training, Mime, 1972 January 03-May 22 (Box 136, Folder 1620)
  - Adult Training, Playwriting, Davey Marlin-Jones, 1968 January 17 (Box 136, Folder 1621)
  - Adult Training, Playwriting, Davey Marlin-Jones, 1968 April 17 (Box 136, Folder 1622)
  - Adult Training, Playwriting, Davey Marlin-Jones, 1968 October 01 (Box 136, Folder 1623)
  - Adult Training, Playwriting, Davey Marlin-Jones, 1969 April 01 (Box 136, Folder 1624)
  - Adult Training, Playwriting, Davey Marlin-Jones, 1969 October 29 (Box 137, Folder 1625)
  - Adult Training, Playwriting, Davey Marlin-Jones Feb., 1970 (Box 137, Folder 1626)
  - Adult Training, Playwriting, Davey Marlin-Jones, 1972 January 03-May 22 (Box 137, Folder 1627)
  - Adult Training, Scene Study, Ed Bordo, 1968 January 22 (Box 137, Folder 1628)
  - Adult Training, Technical Apprenticeship, 1969-1970 (Box 137, Folder 1629)
  - Adult Training, Theater Training, Elaine Funk, 1961 October 02 (Box 137, Folder 1630)
  - Adult Training, Vocal Development, 1972 January 03-May 22 (Box 137, Folder 1631)
  - Adult Training, Scripts, undated (Box 137, Folder 1632)
  - Adult Training, Course Evaluation, 1972-1973 (Box 137, Folder 1633)
  - Adult Training, Other Theater Programs, undated (Box 137, Folder 1634)
  - Junior Stage, Children's Theater Association Operating Code, 1960-1961 (Box 138, Folder 1635)
  - Junior Stage, 1964-1965 (Box 138, Folder 1636)
  - Junior Stage, Frank Johns, 1966-1973 (Box 138, Folder 1637)
  - Junior Stage, Scripts, undated (Box 138, Folder 1638)
  - Junior Stage, Photographs, undated (Box 138, Folder 1639)
  - Junior Stage, Teenage Theater, 1954-1959 (Box 139, Folder 1640)
  - Junior Stage, Teenage Theater, 1960-1967 (Box 139, Folder 1641)
  - Junior Stage, Teenage Registration, 1964-1965 (Box 139, Folder 1642)
  - Junior Stage, Teenage Registration, 1965-1966 (Box 139, Folder 1643)
  - Junior Stage, Teenage Registration, 1966-1967 (Box 139, Folder 1644)
  - Junior Stage, Teenage Theater, 1967-1969 (Box 139, Folder 1645)
  - Junior Stage, Teenage Registration, 1967-1968 (Box 140, Folder 1646)
  - Junior Stage, Teenage Registration, 1968-1969 (Box 140, Folder 1647)
  - Junior Stage, Shenandoah Caverns Proposal, June 16-Aug., 1969 (Box 140, Folder 1648)
  - Junior Stage, Teenage Registration, 1969-1970 (Box 140, Folder 1649)
  - Junior Stage, Teenage Theater, 1970-1973 (Box 140, Folder 1650)
  - Teenage Registration, 1970-1971 (Box 141, Folder 1651)
  - Teenage Registration, 1971-1972 (Box 141, Folder 1652)
  - Teenage Registration, 1972-1973 (Box 141, Folder 1653)
  - Teenage Summer Camp, July 9-Aug.11, 1973 (Box 141, Folder 1654)
  - Teenage Theater Speech Exercises, undated (Box 141, Folder 1655)
  - Teenage Theater Scenes for Classes 1, undated (Box 141, Folder 1656)
  - Teenage Theater Scenes for Classes 2, undated (Box 141, Folder 1657)
  - Teenage Theater Scripts 1, undated (Box 141, Folder 1658)
  - Teenage Theater Scripts 2, undated (Box 142, Folder 1659)
  - Teenage Theater Showcase, undated (Box 142, Folder 1660)
  - Teenage Theater Teaching Material, undated (Box 142, Folder 1661)
  - Teenage Theater Volunteers, undated (Box 142, Folder 1662)
  - Teenage Theater Photographs, undated (Box 142, Folder 1663)
  - Teenage Theater Extension - Anacostia, Hattie M. Strong Grant, 1968 June 11 (Box 143, Folder 1664)
  - Teenage Theater Extension - Anacostia, D.C. Performing Arts Committee, 1968 (Box 143, Folder 1665)
  - Teenage Theater Extension - Anacostia, Citywide Grant 68342, 1968 (Box 143, Folder 1666)
  - Teenage Theater Extension - Anacostia, Citywide Grant 68342, 1968 (Box 143, Folder 1667)
  - Teenage Theater Extension - Anacostia, Program Administration, undated (Box 143, Folder 1668)
  - Teenage Theater Extension - Anacostia, Black Drama's Play, undated (Box 143, Folder 1669)
  - Teenage Theater Extension - Anacostia, Citywide Grant 69252, 1969 (Box 143, Folder 1670)
  - Teenage Theater Extension - Anacostia, Program Administration, undated (Box 143, Folder 1671)
  - Teenage Theater Extension - Anacostia, Hattie M. Strong Grant, 1969 July 08 (Box 143, Folder 1672)
  - Teenage Theater Extension - Anacostia, Citywide Neighborhood Planning Program, 1969-1970 (Box 143, Folder 1673)
  - Teenage Theater Extension - Anacostia, Speech Training, undated (Box 143, Folder 1674)
  - Teenage Theater Extension - Anacostia, Scripts, undated (Box 143, Folder 1675)
  - Teenage Theater Extension - Anacostia, Washington Cultural Center Proposal, 1971 (Box 143, Folder 1676)
  - Teenage Theater Extension - Anacostia, Written by Black Drama Players & Arnold Meyer, undated (Box 143, Folder 1968)
  - Teenage Theater Extension - Anacostia, Leader: John Harris, undated (Box 143, Folder 1969)
  - Teenage Theater Extension - Schools, Private Schools, 1969-1972 (Box 144, Folder 1677)
  - Teenage Theater Extension - Schools, Public Schools, 1967-1973 (Box 144, Folder 1678)
  - Teenage Theater Extension - Schools, Summer in the Parks Teenage Theater Extension - Bowie State College, 1970-1972 (Box 144, Folder 1679)
  - Teenage Theater Extension, Title III Grant, Cooperative Program with Bowie State College Sept., 1969-1974 (Box 144, Folder 1680)
  - Teenage Theater Extension - Bowie State College Grant Planning and Administration. Participants: Elaine Funk, Paul Bennett, & Thomas C. Behrens, 1968-1969 (Box 144, Folder 1681)
  - Teenage Theater Extension - Bowie State College Grant Finances, Oct. - Nov., 1969-1970 (Box 144, Folder 1682)
  - Teenage Theater Extension - Bowie State College Eugene & Agnes E. Meyer Foundation Grant. Proposed - Requested by Bowie, 1969 (Box 144, Folder 1683)
  - Teenage Theater Extension - Bowie State College Promotion, 1969-1970 (Box 145, Folder 1684)
  - Teenage Theater Extension - Bowie State College Class Administration, 1969-1971 (Box 145, Folder 1685)
  - Teenage Theater Extension - Bowie State College Production: Antigone - Jean Anouilh. Oct. 19, undated (Box 145, Folder 1686)
  - Teenage Theater Extension - Bowie State College Production: Prep are for Glory - Ted Shine. May 14-16, undated (Box 145, Folder 1687)
  - Teenage Theater Extension - Bowie State College Grant Planning and Administration. Participants: Elaine Funk & Thomas C. Behrens, 1970-1971 (Box 145, Folder 1688)
  - Teenage Theater Extension - Bowie State College Production: Black Sabbeth, 1970 December 10-12 (Box 145, Folder 1689)
  - Teenage Theater Extension - Bowie State College Bowie State College Curriculum Development, undated (Box 145, Folder 1690)
  - Course Material, undated (Box 145, Folder 1691)
  - Scripts, undated (Box 145, Folder 1692)
  - Outside Performances Attended, undated (Box 145, Folder 1693)
  - Teenage Theater Extension - Bowie State College Place: Smithsonian Institution, undated (Box 145, Folder 1969)
  - Teenage Theater Extension - Bowie State College Controversy with Damon Brazwell, intended director, undated (Box 145, Folder 1970)
  - Teenage Theater Extension, Washington Drama Festival, American University, 1963-1965 (Box 146, Folder 1694)
  - Teenage Theater Extension, Theater Management Interns, American University, undated (Box 146, Folder 1695)
  - Teenage Theater Extension, Theater Management Interns, Georgetown University, 1970 September 28-December 18 (Box 146, Folder 1696)
  - Teenage Theater Extension, Apprentice Program: Workshop for Careers in the Arts, George Washington University, 1970 November 08 (Box 146, Folder 1697)
  - Teenage Theater Extension, In-Service Theater Training, East Carolina College Consortium Contains list of earlier students, 1971-1973 (Box 146, Folder 1698)
  - Teenage Theater Extension, In-Service Theater Training, Beloit College, 1971-1972 (Box 146, Folder 1699)
  - Teenage Theater Extension, In-Service Theater Training, 1972-1973 (Box 146, Folder 1700)
  - Teenage Theater Extension, Coordinator: Mel Meckler, undated (Box 146, Folder 1971)
  - Teenage Theater Extension, In-Service Theater Training Course Material, undated (Box 147, Folder 1701)
  - Teenage Theater Extension, Dramatic Arts Program Proposal, Montgomery College, Aug., undated (Box 147, Folder 1702)
  - Teenage Theater Extension, Theater Seminar Series, Montgomery College, 1972-1973 (Box 147, Folder 1703)
  - Teenage Theater Extension, Use and Training of the Human Voice - Arthur Lessac, undated (Box 147, Folder 1704)
  - Teenage Theater Extension, The Need for Creative Dramatics in the Washington Workshop Program Dolores St. Armand, undated (Box 147, Folder 1705)
  - Teenage Theater Extension, Capitol Institute of Technology Proposal, 1973 December 12 (Box 147, Folder 1706)
  - Teenage Theater Extension, Proposal by Corinne Felton, undated (Box 147, Folder 1972)
  - Theater-in-Education a prospectus, 1967; Series 2 (Box 229, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, press releases, and personnel, 1968-1972; Series 2 (Box 229, Folder 7)
  - The Call newsletter, 1968-1971; Series 2 (Box 229, Folder 8)
  - Playbills, 1967-1970; Series 2 (Box UP0231, Folder 1)
  - Playbills, 1970-1971; Series 2 (Box UP0231, Folder 2)
  - Playbills, 1971-1972; Series 2 (Box UP0231, Folder 3)
  - Playbills, 1972-1973; Series 2 (Box UP0231, Folder 4)
  - Programs, 1966; Series 2 (Box UP0231, Folder 5)
- General Accounting, 1957-1974; MS2061 Series 3
  This series contains ledgers, expenditures, invoices, checks, receipts, pretty cash records, and insurance. The material dates from 1957-1974.
  These records divided into either calendar or fiscal year. The order for the material is Budget, then Ledger, followed by the Expenditures section in an imposed classified order containing invoices, receipts, and petty cash records, under the following headings: building supplies and maintenance, production and office, promotion, subscriptions, box office, and box office for specific productions. Insurance records are also filed in this series. Multiple bank accounts are filed in chronological order. Checks have been retained to supplement the accounting records. The last section of the General Accounts Series contains tax records, and includes Federal, D.C., Maryland, and Virginia taxes.
  - Washington Drama Center Ledger, 1957-1960 (Box 148, Folder 1707)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger, 1959 (Box 148, Folder 1708)
  - Washington Theater Club & Drama Center Budget, 1960 (Box 148, Folder 1709)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger, 1960 (Box 148, Folder 1710)
  - Washington Drama Center Ledger, 1960 (Box 148, Folder 1711)
  - Washington Theater Club Budget, 1961-1962 (Box 148, Folder 1712)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger, 1961 (Box 148, Folder 1713)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger, 1961-1963 (Box 148, Folder 1714)
  - Theater Venture II Ledger 1, 1961-1963 (Box 149, Folder 1715)
  - Theater Venture II Ledger 2, 1961-1963 (Box 149, Folder 1716)
  - Theater Venture II Budget, 1962 (Box 149, Folder 1717)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger, 1962 (Box 149, Folder 1718)
  - Dramatic Arts Society of the District of Columbia Ledger, 1962-1963 (Box 149, Folder 1719)
  - Washington Theater Club Budget, 1963 (Box 149, Folder 1720)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger, 1963 (Box 150, Folder 1721)
  - Washington Drama Center Ledger, 1963 (Box 150, Folder 1722)
  - Washington Theater Club Budget, 1964-1965 (Box 150, Folder 1723)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger, 1964 (Box 150, Folder 1724)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger, 1964-1965 (Box 150, Folder 1725)
  - Washington Theater Club Budget, 1965-1966 (Box 151, Folder 1726)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger, 1965 (Box 151, Folder 1727)
  - Washington Theater Club Budget, 1966-1967 (Box 151, Folder 1728)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger 1, 1966 (Box 151, Folder 1729)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger 2, 1966 (Box 151, Folder 1730)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger 1, 1966-1967 (Box 151, Folder 1731)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger 2, 1966-1967 (Box 152, Folder 1732)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger, 1967 (Box 152, Folder 1733)
  - Washington Theater Club Budget, 1967-1968 (Box 152, Folder 1734)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger 1, 1967-1968 (Box 152, Folder 1735)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger 2, 1967-1968 (Box 153, Folder 1736)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger 3, 1967-1968 (Box 153, Folder 1737)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger 4, 1967-1968 (Box 153, Folder 1738)
  - Washington Theater Club Budget, 1968-1969 (Box 154, Folder 1739)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger, 1968-1969 (Box 154, Folder 1740)
  - Washington Theater Club Budget, 1969-1970 (Box 155, Folder 1741)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger 1, 1969-1970 (Box 155, Folder 1742)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger 2, 1969-1970 (Box 155, Folder 1743)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger 3, 1969-1970 (Box 155, Folder 1744)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger 4, 1969-1970 (Box 156, Folder 1745)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger 5, 1969-1970 (Box 156, Folder 1746)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger 6, 1969-1970 (Box 156, Folder 1747)
  - Washington Theater Club Budget, 1970-1971 (Box 157, Folder 1748)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger 1, 1970-1971 (Box 157, Folder 1749)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger 2, 1970-1971 (Box 157, Folder 1750)
  - Washington Theater Club Budget, 1971-1972 (Box 158, Folder 1751)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger 1, 1971-1972 (Box 158, Folder 1752)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger 2, 1971-1972 (Box 158, Folder 1753)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger 3, 1971-1972 (Box 158, Folder 1754)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger 4, 1971-1972 (Box 159, Folder 1755)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger 5, 1971-1972 (Box 159, Folder 1756)
  - Washington Theater Club Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 159, Folder 1757)
  - Washington Theater Club Ledger, 1972-1973 (Box 159, Folder 1758)
  - Expenditures Building Supplies & Maintenance, 1957-1958 (Box 160, Folder 1759)
  - Expenditures Production & Office, 1957-1958 (Box 160, Folder 1760)
  - Expenditures Promotion, 1957-1958 (Box 160, Folder 1761)